Sheet Music Collection UA064
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Sheet music collection, 1883 -- 1943; 1900 -- 1920; UA064.001; 3.45 Linear Feet
  - That's Why [Text and Melody], 1930; UA064.001.001.00147; Bean, Norman S. (Box 1)
    Text and Melody.
  - Things I'll Never Do, 1913; UA064.001.001.00148; Bullard, Carrie (Box 1)
  - Three Cheers for your Uncle Sam [Band Cards], 1917; UA064.001.001.00149; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
    Band Cards; Full Band.
  - Three Cheers for your Uncle Sam [Chorus Training Sheet], 1917; UA064.001.001.00150; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
    Chorus Training Sheet.
  - Three Cheers for your Uncle Sam [Full Band B-flat], 1917; UA064.001.001.00151; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
    Full Band in B-flat.
  - Three Cheers for your Uncle Sam [March with Chorus], 1917; UA064.001.001.00152; Lewis, Leo Rich; Waterman, Nixon (Box 1)
    March with Chorus.
  - Three Cheers for your Uncle Sam [Small Orchestra Score], 1917; UA064.001.001.00153; Lewis, Leo Rich; Waterman, Nixon (Box 1)
    Small Orchestra Score.
  - Three Cheers for your Uncle Sam [Song Cards], 1917; UA064.001.001.00154; Lewis, Leo Rich; Waterman, Nixon (Box 1)
    Song Cards.
  - Three-Pt. Invention, 1926; UA064.001.001.00155; Cunningham, W. A. (Box 1)
  - Tick Tock Toe [Glee Club, Tenor & Bass], 1937; UA064.001.001.00156; Bullard, Frederick Field (Box 1)
    Glee Club Parts, Tenor & Bass.
  - Tribute to Alma Mater, 1914; UA064.001.001.00157; Hearsey, Evelyn; Hearsey, Helen (Box 1)
    For Class Day, 1914.
  - Tuftonian Rhapsody, 1922; UA064.001.001.00158; Lamont, R.R. (Box 1)
    For Class Day, 1916.
  - Tuftonia's Day [1912], 1913; UA064.001.001.00159; Hayes, Elliott W. (Box 1)
    A Song of Tufts College.
  - Tuftonia's Day [Full Band], 1913; UA064.001.001.00160; Hayes, Elliott W. (Box 1)
    The Music of Tufts College Serial Number 286; Full Band Arrangement.
  - Tuftonia's Day [Full Orchestra], 1913; UA064.001.001.00161; Hayes, Elliott W. (Box 1)
  - A Tufts "Bodun" Song, 1915; UA064.001.001.00162; Garabedian, Carl A. (Box 1)
    Melody and Text.
  - Tufts College Music [compilation], 1915; UA064.001.001.00163; Brooks, William Gooch (Box 1)
    Parent of Light; Tufts Today, For Aye!; Tuftonian Rhapsody.
  - The Tufts Girl, 1906; UA064.001.001.00164 (Box 1)
    Jackson Glee Club.
  - Tufts Today, for Aye! [Full Band], 1910 -- 1915; UA064.001.001.00165; Brooks, William Gooch (Box 1)
    The Music of Tufts College Serial Number 211; Full Band.
  - Tufts Today, for Aye! [Glee Club], 1915; UA064.001.001.00166 (Box 1)
    Glee Club.
  - Tufts Today, for Aye! [Piano Copy], 1915; UA064.001.001.00167; Brooks, William Gooch (Box 1)
    Piano Copy
  - Tufts Today for Aye! [Song Book], 1915; UA064.001.001.00168; Brooks, William Gooch; French, H. M. (Box 1)
    Song Book.
  - Tufts Today, Tufts for Aye! [Medium Orchestra], 1915; UA064.001.001.00169; Brooks, William Gooch; French, H. M. (Box 1)
    Medium Orchestra Arrangement; The Music of Tufts College Serial Number 41.
  - Tufts Victory Song [Medium Orchestra], 1915; UA064.001.001.00170; Rose, W.W. (Box 1)
    Medium Orchestra Arrangement; The Music of Tufts College Serial Number 23.
  - Tufts Victory Song [Unison Chorus], 1911; UA064.001.001.00171; Rose, W.W.; Gott, Charles (Box 1)
    Unison Chorus.
  - Twentieth Tufts Night at the Pops, 1932; UA064.001.001.00172; Hayes, Elliott W.; French, H. M.; Brooks, William Gooch; Gott, Charles; Rose, W.W.; Maulsby, David Lee; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
    Tuftonia's Day; Dear Alma Mater; Tufts Today, Tufts for Aye; Tufts Victory Song.
  - Twenty-five current songs from the book of Tufts music, 1925; UA064.001.001.00173 (Box 1)
    Alma Mater's Day; Aren't You Glad; Barnum Song Chorus; Bodun Song; Brown and Blue; Brown and Blue Forever; Charlie Tufts His College; Cheer for the Team; Dear Alma Mater; Fight, Tufts, Fight!; For Tufts Hurrah!; Forward, Tufts!; Hail, Tufts; In Praise of Alma Mater; Keep Your Eye on Tufts; Loyalty; Spell it Out; That Mascot; Tribute to Alma Mater; Tuftonia's Day; Tufts Today; Victory Song; We Love It for Aye; Win
  - Twenty-Fourth Tufts Night at the Pops, 1936; UA064.001.001.00174; Newton, E.W.; Maulsby, David Lee; Hayes, Elliott W.; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
    Tuftonia's Day; Te Salatamus; Chorus of Barnum Song; Brown and Blue; Dear Alma Mater; That's Why.
  - Twenty-third Night at the Pops, 1935; UA064.001.001.00175; Hayes, Elliott W.; Brooks, William Gooch; French, H. M.; Maulsby, David Lee; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
    Tufts Today, Tufts For Aye; Brown and Blue; Tuftonia's Day; Dear Alma Mater.
  - Two Choruses, 1936; UA064.001.001.00176; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
    Eventide; Sun-Up.
  - The Voice of Alma Mater [Class Song of 1912], UA064.001.001.00177; Rose, W.W.; Bradford, Edith H. (Box 1)
    Class Song of 1912.
  - We Stand [card], 1918; UA064.001.001.00178; Lewis, Leo Rich; PLatt, C. D. (Box 1)
  - We Stand [Church Card], 1918; UA064.001.001.00179; Lewis, Leo Rich; PLatt, C. D. (Box 1)
    Church Card.
  - We Stand [Coda for Male Voices], 1918; UA064.001.001.00180; PLatt, C. D.; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
    Coda for Male Voices.
  - We Stand [Coda for Mixed Voices], 1918; UA064.001.001.00181; PLatt, C. D.; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 1)
    Coda for Mixed Voices.
  - We Stand [For Baritone Solo and Mixed Chorus], 1918; UA064.001.001.00182; Lewis, Leo Rich; PLatt, C. D. (Box 1)
    For Baritone Solo, Mixed Chorus or Quartet, and Organ.
  - We Stand [For Unison Chorus in C], 1918; UA064.001.001.00183; Lewis, Leo Rich; PLatt, C. D. (Box 1)
    For Unison Chorus in C.
  - We Stand [Full, C, 16mo], 1918; UA064.001.001.00184; Lewis, Leo Rich; PLatt, C. D. (Box 1)
    Full Band in C.
  - We Stand [Full, D-flat, 16mo], 1918; UA064.001.001.00185; Lewis, Leo Rich; PLatt, C. D. (Box 1)
    Full Band in D-flat.
  - We Stand [Pennysheet Series], 1918; UA064.001.001.00186; Lewis, Leo Rich; PLatt, C. D. (Box 1)
    Pennysheet Series.
  - We Stand [Song Music], 1918; UA064.001.001.00187; Lewis, Leo Rich; PLatt, C. D. (Box 1)
    Song Music.
  - Alma Mater's Day [Full Edition in D-flat], 1916; UA064.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - Andante from Op. 7. [Twilight], 1922; UA064.001.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - Barnum Song, 1936; UA064.001.002.00003 (Box 2)
  - Bonds of Light, Class Song of 1939, UA064.001.002.00004 (Box 2)
  - Brown and Blue [Orchestra Parts], 1939; UA064.001.002.00005; Newton, E.W. (Box 2)
    Full Orchestra; Orchestrated by Willis, '01, and Adkins, '39
  - Brown and Blue Forever [Full Orchestra], 1923; UA064.001.002.00006; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 2)
  - Campus Song., 1896; UA064.001.002.00007; Bullard, Frederick Field (Box 2)
  - The Captivity, 1938; UA064.001.002.00008; Bullard, Carrie (Box 2)
  - Class Day [Full Score], 1936; UA064.001.002.00009 (Box 2)
    Full Score.
  - Class Song of 1905, UA064.001.002.00010 (Box 2)
  - Class Song of 1910, UA064.001.002.00011 (Box 2)
  - Class Song of 1938., UA064.001.002.00012 (Box 2)
  - Concertino for Trumpet [Solo Trumpet], 1943; UA064.001.002.00013; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 2)
  - Concertino for Trumpet [Piano Reduction], 1943; UA064.001.002.00014; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 2)
  - Concertino for Trumpet [String Parts], 1943; UA064.001.002.00015; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 2)
  - Dear Alma Mater [For Symphonic Orchestra], 1935; UA064.001.002.00016 (Box 2)
    Symphonic Orchestra.
  - Dear Alma Mater [Score], 1936; UA064.001.002.00017 (Box 2)
    Score.
  - Fight [Score for Military Band], 1930; UA064.001.002.00018; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 2)
    Score for Military Band.
  - Forward! [Full Military Band in E-flat], 1938; UA064.001.002.00019 (Box 2)
    Full Military Band in E-flat.
  - Greeting, Class Song of Tufts College, 1941; UA064.001.002.00020 (Box 2)
  - Hard to Please., 1936; UA064.001.002.00021 (Box 2)
  - Intercollegiate Inklings [Parts], UA064.001.002.00022 (Box 2)
    parts.
  - In the Land where dreams come true by John W. Metcalf, 1913; UA064.001.002.00023 (Box 2)
  - Inventions., 1933; UA064.001.002.00024; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 2)
  - The Jumbo Victory March, Tufts Music No. 303, 1939; UA064.001.002.00025 (Box 2)
  - Loyalty, 1938; UA064.001.003.00001 (Box 3)
  - Medley Fantasia on Tufts Airs [For Symphonic Orchestra], 1937; UA064.001.003.00002; Morton, J.W. (Box 3)
    For Symphonic Orchestra.
  - Medley Fantasia on Tufts Airs [Full Band Arrangement], 1925; UA064.001.003.00003; Morton, J.W. (Box 3)
    Full Band Arrangement.
  - Moo-Cow-Moo, 1913; UA064.001.003.00004; Bullard, Carrie (Box 3)
  - North and South [For General Singing in B-flat], 1918; UA064.001.003.00005 (Box 3)
    For General Sining; B-flat.
  - Old Fortunatus [276; Conductor's Score], 1937; UA064.001.003.00006; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 3)
  - Old Fortunatus [277: I Flute or Violin Alternate], 1937; UA064.001.003.00007; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 3)
  - Old Fortunatus [278: II Flute or Violin I], 1937; UA064.001.003.00008; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 3)
  - Old Fortunatus [279: III Oboe or Violin II], 1937; UA064.001.003.00009; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 3)
  - Old Fortunatus [280: IVa Clarinet in B-flat], 1937; UA064.001.003.00010; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 3)
  - Old Fortunatus [281 IVb Viola, Alternate of Clarinet], 1937; UA064.001.003.00011; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 3)
  - Old Fortunatus [282 V Bassoon or Violoncello], 1937; UA064.001.003.00012; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 3)
  - Old Fortunatus [283 VI The Songs], 1937; UA064.001.003.00013; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 3)
  - An Old Time Celebration [Festival tone sketch in March form], 1926; UA064.001.003.00014 (Box 3)
  - The Rose and the Ring [Overture and Finale of Act I--Score], 1933; UA064.001.004.00001; Bullard, Carrie (Box 4)
  - The Rose and the Ring [Overture and Finale of Act I--Parts], 1934; UA064.001.004.00002; Bullard, Carrie (Box 4)
  - The Rose and the Ring [Act One Score], 1934; UA064.001.004.00003; Bullard, Carrie (Box 4)
    Act One.
  - The Rose and the Ring [Act Two Score], 1934; UA064.001.004.00004; Bullard, Carrie (Box 4)
    Act Two.
  - The Rose and the Ring [Act One, First Violin], 1934; UA064.001.004.00005; Bullard, Carrie (Box 4)
    Act One; First Violin.
  - The Rose and the Ring [Act One, Second Violin], 1934; UA064.001.004.00006; Bullard, Carrie (Box 4)
    Act One; Second Violin.
  - The Rose and the Ring [Act One, Viola], 1934; UA064.001.004.00007; Bullard, Carrie (Box 4)
    Act One; Viola.
  - The Rose and the Ring [Act One, Violoncello], 1934; UA064.001.004.00008; Bullard, Carrie (Box 4)
    Act One; Violoncello.
  - The Rose and the Ring [Flute, Act one and two], 1934; UA064.001.004.00009; Bullard, Carrie (Box 4)
    Flute, Act One and Two.
  - The Rose and the Ring [Act One, Oboe], 1934; UA064.001.004.00010; Bullard, Carrie (Box 4)
    Act One, Oboe.
  - The Rose and the Ring [Act One, Clarinet], 1934; UA064.001.004.00011; Bullard, Carrie (Box 4)
    Act One, Clarinet.
  - The Rose and the Ring [Act One, Bassoon], 1934; UA064.001.004.00012; Bullard, Carrie (Box 4)
    Act One, Bassoon.
  - The Rose and the Ring [Act One, Horn], 1934; UA064.001.004.00013; Bullard, Carrie (Box 4)
    Act One; Horn.
  - The Rose and the Ring [Act One, Trumpet], 1934; UA064.001.004.00014; Bullard, Carrie (Box 4)
    Act One; Trumpet.
  - The Rose and the Ring [Act One, Trombone], 1934; UA064.001.004.00015; Bullard, Carrie (Box 4)
    Act One; Trombone.
  - The Rose and the Ring [Act One, Kettle Drums], 1934; UA064.001.004.00016; Bullard, Carrie (Box 4)
    Act One; Kettle Drums.
  - The Rose and the Ring [Act One, Drums], 1934; UA064.001.004.00017 (Box 4)
    Act ONe; Drums.
  - The Rose and the Ring [Act Two, First Violin], 1934; UA064.001.004.00018; Bullard, Carrie (Box 4)
    Act Two; First Violin.
  - The Rose and the Ring [Act Two, Second Violin], 1934; UA064.001.004.00019; Bullard, Carrie (Box 4)
    Act Two; Second Violin.
  - The Rose and the Ring [Act Two, Violoncello], 1934; UA064.001.004.00020; Bullard, Carrie (Box 4)
    Act Two; violoncello.
  - The Rose and the Ring [Act Two, Bass], 1934; UA064.001.004.00021; Bullard, Carrie (Box 4)
    Act Two; Bass.
  - The Rose and the Ring [Act Two, First Clarinet], 1934; UA064.001.004.00022; Bullard, Carrie (Box 4)
    Act Two; First Clarinet.
  - The Rose and the Ring [Act Two, First Trumpet], 1934; UA064.001.004.00023; Bullard, Carrie (Box 4)
    Act Two; First Trumpet.
  - The Rose and the Ring [Act Two, Horns 1 & 2], 1934; UA064.001.004.00024; Bullard, Carrie (Box 4)
    Act Two; Horns 1 & 2.
  - Second String Quartet [Parts], 1940; UA064.001.005.00001 (Box 5)
  - Some Little Bug., 1932; UA064.001.005.00002 (Box 5)
  - Sonata for Pianoforte and Violin., 1894; UA064.001.005.00003 (Box 5)
  - Song of the Awakening [Organ Accompaniment], 1936; UA064.001.005.00004; Lamont, R.R. (Box 5)
  - Swedish Folksong., 1923; UA064.001.005.00005; Lamont, R.R. (Box 5)
  - Symphonic Prelude for Symphonic Orchestra, 1936; UA064.001.005.00006; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 5)
  - Symphonic Prelude [Full Score], 1936; UA064.001.005.00007; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 5)
  - Symphonic Prelude [Piano I and II], 1936; UA064.001.005.00008; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 5)
  - That's Why! [Orchestra Parts], 1930; UA064.001.005.00009; Bean, Norman S.; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 5)
  - Three Cheers for your Uncle Sam., 1918; UA064.001.005.00010 (Box 5)
    March Song; March with Chorus; and March-song for Camp, Shipboard, Campaign, College, School or Home.
  - Three Songs for Medium Voice [A king lived long ago, Lonliness, Invitation], 1936; UA064.001.005.00011 (Box 5)
    A King Lived Long Ago; Lonliness; An Invitation.
  - Tuftonian Rhapsody [Full Score], 1939; UA064.001.005.00012; Lewis, Leo Rich (Box 5)
  - Tuftonian Rhapsody [Orchestra Parts], 1939; UA064.001.005.00013; Lamont, R.R. (Box 5)
  - Twenty Seventh Tufts Night at the pops, "Tuftonia's Day", 1939; UA064.001.005.00014 (Box 5)
  - Twilight [Andante from Op 7-Orchestra Parts], 1922; UA064.001.005.00015 (Box 5)
    For Orchestra.
  - The Upward Path, Class Song of 1937, UA064.001.005.00016 (Box 5)
  - We Stand [Song Edition], 1918; UA064.001.005.00017 (Box 5)
    Song Edition.
  - Wise Old Neptune [Second Act], 1938; UA064.001.005.00018; Bullard, Carrie (Box 5)
    Second Act.
  - Where'er You Walk, 1938; UA064.001.005.00019; Lamont, R.R. (Box 5)
  - Encore Songs [Tick Tack Toe - Low Voice], 1903; UA064.001.006.00001; Bullard, Frederick Field (Box 6)
    Tick Tack Toe; Low Voice.
  - Encore Songs [Tick Tack Toe - Medium Voice], 1903; UA064.001.006.00002; Bullard, Frederick Field (Box 6)
    Tick Tack Toe; Medium Voice.
  - The Fern Song by Fredrick Field Bullard, 1913; UA064.001.006.00003 (Box 6)
  - Four Songs, Opus 3 by F.F. Bullard, 1903; UA064.001.006.00004 (Box 6)
  - The Heart of the World by F.F. Bullard, 1896; UA064.001.006.00006 (Box 6)
  - Kruglied, Frederick Field Bullard, 1898; UA064.001.006.00008 (Box 6)
  - Lass of Norwick-town, F.F. Bullard, 1899; UA064.001.006.00009 (Box 6)
  - Love came down from out the sky, F.F. Bullard, UA064.001.006.00010 (Box 6)
  - Love me, love me not, F.F. Bullard, 1897; UA064.001.006.00011 (Box 6)
  - The Monk of the Mountain, F.F. Bullard, 1913; UA064.001.006.00012 (Box 6)
  - Opus 8, Frederick F. Bullard, 1894; UA064.001.006.00013 (Box 6)
  - Remind me Sweeting, F.F. Bullard, 1913; UA064.001.006.00014 (Box 6)
  - A Stein Song, F.F. Bullard, 1898; UA064.001.006.00015 (Box 6)
  - O Stern old land, F.F. Bullard, 1913; UA064.001.006.00016 (Box 6)
  - Sword of Ferrera, F.F. Bullard, 1899; UA064.001.006.00017 (Box 6)
  - The Sword of Ferrara, Bb, F.F. Bullard, 1899; UA064.001.006.00018 (Box 6)
  - There is one way and only one way, F.F. Bullard, 1899; UA064.001.006.00019 (Box 6)
  - There's a woman like a dewdrop, F.F. Bullard, 1913; UA064.001.006.00020 (Box 6)
  - Three Cavalier Songs, F. F. Bullard, 1920; UA064.001.006.00021 (Box 6)
  - Compositions by Frederick Field Bullard [Tick, Tack, Toe], 1903; UA064.001.006.00022; Bullard, Frederick Field (Box 6)
    Tick, Tack, Toe.
  - The Waterlily, Frederick Field Bullard, 1913; UA064.001.006.00024 (Box 6)
  - You remind me sweeting, Serenade, by Frederick Field Bullard, 1913; UA064.001.006.00025 (Box 6)
  - You shall not go, F.F. Bullard, 1899; UA064.001.006.00026 (Box 6)
  - Where to go to [Tenor and Bass Parts; Full Voice], 1913; UA064.001.007.00001; Merrill, M. H. (Box 7)
    Tenor and Bass Parts; Full Voice.
  - The Whispered Song, 1913; UA064.001.007.00002; Bullard, Carrie (Box 7)
    Medium Voice in B-flat.
  - Why?, 1913; UA064.001.007.00003; Bullard, Carrie (Box 7)
    Medium Voice in G.
  - Word Book of Tufts Songs, 1915; UA064.001.007.00004 (Box 7)
  - The World, 1917; UA064.001.007.00005; Bullard, Carrie (Box 7)
    Part Song for School or Mixed Voices.
  - The Music of Tufts College [Compilation], 1942; UA064.001.007.00006; Hayes, Elliott W.; Burns, Edward G.; MacKillop Jr., Kenneth (Box 7)
    Jack and Jill; Te Salutamus. Date is approximate
  - For Goddard! Three Times Three!, 1919; UA064.001.007.00007; Stone, David; Lamont, R.R. (Box 7)
  - Tufts Forever, 1940; UA064.001.007.00008; Bodge, J. Everett; Flandreau, Sandy (Box 7)
    Date is approximate
  - We Would Be Building, 1936; UA064.001.007.00009; Deitz, Purd E.; Sibelius, Jean (Box 7)
  - Tufts Text-Melody Collection: Twenty-five current songs from The Book of Tufts Music, 1925; UA064.001.007.00010; Lewis, Leo R. (Box 7)
  - Class Song of 1886, 1911; UA064.001.002.00026; .1 Linear Feet 1 folder (Box 2, Box 26)
    Class Song of 1886, printed for Tufts Reunion in 1911.
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    Donated by Barry Levy, 2015, accession 2015.052.